{
  "french": {
    "level1": {
      "qn1": {
        "answer": "Technology",
        "options": [
          "Credit",
          "Majority",
          "Technology",
          "Camera"
        ],
        "question": "Technologie"
      },
      "qn10": {
        "answer": "Pour",
        "options": [
          "Finish",
          "Expect",
          "Pour",
          "Smoke"
        ],
        "question": "Verser"
      },
      "qn2": {
        "answer": "Show",
        "options": [
          "Show",
          "Vision",
          "Color",
          "Crowd"
        ],
        "question": "Spectacle"
      },
      "qn3": {
        "answer": "Director",
        "options": [
          "Lack",
          "President",
          "Director",
          "Number"
        ],
        "question": "Réalisateur"
      },
      "qn4": {
        "answer": "Hand",
        "options": [
          "Brother",
          "Support",
          "Hand",
          "Ability"
        ],
        "question": "Main"
      },
      "qn5": {
        "answer": "Concern",
        "options": [
          "Manager",
          "Beach",
          "Concern",
          "Ability"
        ],
        "question": "Inquiétude"
      },
      "qn6": {
        "answer": "Memory",
        "options": [
          "Service",
          "Memory",
          "Sample",
          "Committee"
        ],
        "question": "Souvenir"
      },
      "qn7": {
        "answer": "Massive",
        "options": [
          "Massive",
          "Consistent",
          "Afraid",
          "Actual"
        ],
        "question": "Imposant"
      },
      "qn8": {
        "answer": "Fast",
        "options": [
          "Direct",
          "Wild",
          "Fast",
          "Horrible"
        ],
        "question": "Rapide"
      },
      "qn9": {
        "answer": "Catch",
        "options": [
          "Quote",
          "Witness",
          "Catch",
          "Comfort"
        ],
        "question": "Attraper"
      }
    },
    "level2": {
      "qn1": {
        "answer": "Thousand",
        "options": [
          "Thousand",
          "Hundred",
          "Fifty",
          "One"
        ],
        "question": "Mille"
      },
      "qn10": {
        "answer": "Skip",
        "options": [
          "Tip",
          "Distroy",
          "Skip",
          "Adjust"
        ],
        "question": "Sauter"
      },
      "qn2": {
        "answer": "Fifty",
        "options": [
          "Fifty",
          "Thousand",
          "Five",
          "Thirty"
        ],
        "question": "Cinquante"
      },
      "qn3": {
        "answer": "Three",
        "options": [
          "Seven",
          "Thousand",
          "Three",
          "Nine"
        ],
        "question": "Trois"
      },
      "qn4": {
        "answer": "Zero",
        "options": [
          "Two",
          "Sixty",
          "Zero",
          "Ten"
        ],
        "question": "Zéro"
      },
      "qn5": {
        "answer": "Model",
        "options": [
          "Edge",
          "Model",
          "Window",
          "Majority"
        ],
        "question": "Mannequin"
      },
      "qn6": {
        "answer": "Head",
        "options": [
          "Human",
          "Case",
          "Head",
          "Cup"
        ],
        "question": "Téte"
      },
      "qn7": {
        "answer": "Shoulder",
        "options": [
          "Shoulder",
          "Study",
          "Number",
          "Majority"
        ],
        "question": "Epaule"
      },
      "qn8": {
        "answer": "Agreement",
        "options": [
          "Town",
          "Baby",
          "Agreement",
          "Answer"
        ],
        "question": "Accord"
      },
      "qn9": {
        "answer": "Read",
        "options": [
          "Read",
          "Speak",
          "Play",
          "Transfer"
        ],
        "question": "Lire"
      }
    },
    "level3": {
      "qn1": {
        "answer": "Well done!",
        "options": [
          "I don't like it",
          "Well done!",
          "Not yet",
          "Thank you"
        ],
        "question": "Bien joué !"
      },
      "qn10": {
        "answer": "Open the door",
        "options": [
          "A round trip ticket",
          "I'm coming right now",
          "Open the door",
          "Ri ht there"
        ],
        "question": "Ouvre la porte"
      },
      "qn2": {
        "answer": "Who are they?",
        "options": [
          "Who are they?",
          "Where is he?",
          "What time is it?",
          "Are you sure?"
        ],
        "question": "Qui sont-ils ?"
      },
      "qn3": {
        "answer": "Just a little",
        "options": [
          "Good morning",
          "I agree",
          "Just a little",
          "I have money"
        ],
        "question": "Juste un petit peu"
      },
      "qn4": {
        "answer": "That looks old",
        "options": [
          "That looks old",
          "Thank you",
          "If you need my help, please let me know",
          "I still haven't decided"
        ],
        "question": "Ça a l'air vieux"
      },
      "qn5": {
        "answer": "We're late",
        "options": [
          "We're late",
          "Be careful",
          "Come here",
          "I still haven't decided"
        ],
        "question": "Nous sommes en retard"
      },
      "qn6": {
        "answer": "Someone is coming",
        "options": [
          "I want to ask you a question",
          "Please tell me",
          "Someone is coming",
          "Please"
        ],
        "question": "Quelqu'un vient"
      },
      "qn7": {
        "answer": "How do you spell the word?",
        "options": [
          "Am I pronouncing it correctly?",
          "How do you say it?",
          "How do you spell the word?",
          "What does this say?"
        ],
        "question": "Comment épelles-tu le mot ?"
      },
      "qn8": {
        "answer": "Can you do me a favor?",
        "options": [
          "Excuse me, what did you say?",
          "How do you pronounce that?",
          "Can you do me a favor?",
          "Can you translate this for me?"
        ],
        "question": "Peux-tu me rendre un service ?"
      },
      "qn9": {
        "answer": "It's north of here",
        "options": [
          "Go straight ahead",
          "It's north of here",
          "You have a very nice car",
          "Turn right"
        ],
        "question": "C'est au nord d'ici."
      }
    }
  },
  "german": {
    "level1": {
      "qn1": {
        "answer": "Good Morning",
        "options": [
          "Good Morning",
          "Good Afternoon",
          "Good Evening",
          "Good Night"
        ],
        "question": "Guten Morgen"
      },
      "qn10": {
        "answer": "Work",
        "options": [
          "Armour",
          "Also",
          "After",
          "Work"
        ],
        "question": "Arbeit"
      },
      "qn2": {
        "answer": "Milk",
        "options": [
          "Mother",
          "Milk",
          "Man",
          "Musk"
        ],
        "question": "Milch"
      },
      "qn3": {
        "answer": "Hello",
        "options": [
          "Hello",
          "Hi",
          "Good Morning",
          "Water"
        ],
        "question": "Hallo"
      },
      "qn4": {
        "answer": "Wine",
        "options": [
          "Vienna",
          "Veet",
          "Wine",
          "Wise"
        ],
        "question": "der Wein"
      },
      "qn5": {
        "answer": "Bye",
        "options": [
          "Hi",
          "Bye",
          "Good bye",
          "See you later"
        ],
        "question": "tschüss"
      },
      "qn6": {
        "answer": "As",
        "options": [
          "After",
          "Although",
          "As",
          "Also"
        ],
        "question": "auch"
      },
      "qn7": {
        "answer": "Great",
        "options": [
          "Okay",
          "Tell",
          "Great",
          "Teach"
        ],
        "question": "Toll"
      },
      "qn8": {
        "answer": "Boy Friend",
        "options": [
          "Boy Friend",
          "Fish",
          "Family",
          "Girl Friend"
        ],
        "question": "Freund"
      },
      "qn9": {
        "answer": "Girl Friend",
        "options": [
          "Family",
          "Girl Friend",
          "Boy Friend",
          "Fish"
        ],
        "question": "Freundin"
      }
    },
    "level2": {
      "qn1": {
        "answer": "Two",
        "options": [
          "One",
          "Two",
          "Three",
          "Four"
        ],
        "question": "Zwei"
      },
      "qn10": {
        "answer": "Too small",
        "options": [
          "Too small",
          "Soo small",
          "Too clean",
          "Soo clean"
        ],
        "question": "Zu klein"
      },
      "qn2": {
        "answer": "Three",
        "options": [
          "Two",
          "One",
          "Three",
          "Four"
        ],
        "question": "Drei"
      },
      "qn3": {
        "answer": "One",
        "options": [
          "One",
          "Two",
          "Three",
          "Four"
        ],
        "question": "Eins"
      },
      "qn4": {
        "answer": "Nine",
        "options": [
          "One",
          "Nine",
          "No",
          "Nill"
        ],
        "question": "Neun"
      },
      "qn5": {
        "answer": "Grandmother",
        "options": [
          "Grandmother",
          "Grandfather",
          "Father",
          "Mother"
        ],
        "question": "Oma"
      },
      "qn6": {
        "answer": "Grandfather",
        "options": [
          "Grandmother",
          "Grandfather",
          "Father",
          "Mother"
        ],
        "question": "Opa"
      },
      "qn7": {
        "answer": "Mother",
        "options": [
          "Grandmother",
          "Grandfather",
          "Father",
          "Mother"
        ],
        "question": "Mutter"
      },
      "qn8": {
        "answer": "Father",
        "options": [
          "Grandmother",
          "Grandfather",
          "Father",
          "Mother"
        ],
        "question": "Vater"
      },
      "qn9": {
        "answer": "Paint",
        "options": [
          "Man",
          "Paint",
          "Husband",
          "Mate"
        ],
        "question": "Male"
      }
    },
    "level3": {
      "qn1": {
        "answer": "Vergiss es",
        "options": [
          "Den gazen Tag",
          "Es funktioniert",
          "Vergiss es",
          "Ich bin einverstanden"
        ],
        "question": "Forget it"
      },
      "qn10": {
        "answer": "It's very cold today",
        "options": [
          "It's raining today",
          "It's very windy today",
          "It's very cold today",
          "It's really hot today"
        ],
        "question": "Heute ist es sehr kalt."
      },
      "qn2": {
        "answer": "You stepped on me. I'm sorry",
        "options": [
          "Thank you for your continued support",
          "You stepped on me. I'm sorry",
          "Success is the result of hardword",
          "My fater is a taxi driver"
        ],
        "question": "Du bist auf mich getreten. Tut mir leid."
      },
      "qn3": {
        "answer": "Can I see your passport please?",
        "options": [
          "Can I see your passport please?",
          "What do you think of these shoes?",
          "Did you complete the assigment on time?",
          "Is this a dream or is this a reality?"
        ],
        "question": "Kann ich bitte Ihren Pass sehen?"
      },
      "qn4": {
        "answer": "What do they study?",
        "options": [
          "How do I use this?",
          "How do you know?",
          "What do they study?",
          "Where did it happen?"
        ],
        "question": "Was studieren sie"
      },
      "qn5": {
        "answer": "Do you hear that?",
        "options": [
          "Do you hear that?",
          "How many?",
          "How are you?",
          "Where did you go?"
        ],
        "question": "Hörtst du das"
      },
      "qn6": {
        "answer": "What do you have?",
        "options": [
          "What do you have?",
          "Do you go there often?",
          "Which one is better",
          "Who won?"
        ],
        "question": "Was hast du?"
      },
      "qn7": {
        "answer": "Why not?",
        "options": [
          "Why not?",
          "At what time did it happen",
          "Can you show me?",
          "Do you know what this says?"
        ],
        "question": "Wieso nicht?"
      },
      "qn8": {
        "answer": "Do you have a girlfriend?",
        "options": [
          "Are they coming this evening?",
          "Do you like your co-workers?",
          "Do you have a girlfriend?",
          "How's business"
        ],
        "question": "Hast du eine Freudin"
      },
      "qn9": {
        "answer": "How tall are you?",
        "options": [
          "How tall are you?",
          "How many people do you have in your family?",
          "What do you study?",
          "Can you hold this for me?"
        ],
        "question": "Wie groß bist du?"
      }
    }
  },
  "italian": {
    "level1": {
      "qn1": {
        "answer": "Nature",
        "options": [
          "Research",
          "Section",
          "Nature",
          "Village"
        ],
        "question": "Natura"
      },
      "qn10": {
        "answer": "Unlikely",
        "options": [
          "Unlikely",
          "Talented",
          "Average",
          "Brilliant"
        ],
        "question": "Improbabile"
      },
      "qn2": {
        "answer": "Paper",
        "options": [
          "Officer",
          "Violence",
          "Paper",
          "Crowd"
        ],
        "question": "Carta"
      },
      "qn3": {
        "answer": "Fact",
        "options": [
          "Size",
          "Fact",
          "Responsibility",
          "Office"
        ],
        "question": "Fatto"
      },
      "qn4": {
        "answer": "Store",
        "options": [
          "Article",
          "Space",
          "Store",
          "Judge"
        ],
        "question": "Negozio"
      },
      "qn5": {
        "answer": "Call",
        "options": [
          "Call",
          "Conversation",
          "Line",
          "Difference"
        ],
        "question": "Chiamata"
      },
      "qn6": {
        "answer": "Jacket",
        "options": [
          "Country",
          "Jacket",
          "Egg",
          "Village"
        ],
        "question": "Giacca"
      },
      "qn7": {
        "answer": "History",
        "options": [
          "History",
          "Picture",
          "Sign",
          "Subject"
        ],
        "question": "Storia"
      },
      "qn8": {
        "answer": "Raw",
        "options": [
          "Complex",
          "Raw",
          "External",
          "Average"
        ],
        "question": "Cruda"
      },
      "qn9": {
        "answer": "Hungry",
        "options": [
          "Odd",
          "Hungry",
          "Right",
          "Soft"
        ],
        "question": "Affamato"
      }
    },
    "level2": {
      "qn1": {
        "answer": "Seven",
        "options": [
          "Seven",
          "Four",
          "Ninety",
          "Hundred"
        ],
        "question": "Sette"
      },
      "qn10": {
        "answer": "Gray",
        "options": [
          "Rich",
          "Public",
          "Gray",
          "Widesperad"
        ],
        "question": "Grigio"
      },
      "qn2": {
        "answer": "Five",
        "options": [
          "Billion",
          "Five",
          "Four",
          "Fifty"
        ],
        "question": "Cinque"
      },
      "qn3": {
        "answer": "Nine",
        "options": [
          "Nine",
          "Eight",
          "Five",
          "Fourteen"
        ],
        "question": "Nove"
      },
      "qn4": {
        "answer": "Enjoy",
        "options": [
          "Enjoy",
          "Rush",
          "Plant",
          "Promote"
        ],
        "question": "Piacere"
      },
      "qn5": {
        "answer": "Dissolve",
        "options": [
          "Pick",
          "Dissolve",
          "Bear",
          "Quit"
        ],
        "question": "Dissolvere"
      },
      "qn6": {
        "answer": "Hurt",
        "options": [
          "Hurt",
          "Call",
          "Affect",
          "Suppose"
        ],
        "question": "Far male"
      },
      "qn7": {
        "answer": "Excuse",
        "options": [
          "Excuse",
          "Calm",
          "Care",
          "Snap"
        ],
        "question": "Scusare"
      },
      "qn8": {
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
          "Sunday",
          "April",
          "March",
          "July"
        ],
        "question": "Domenica"
      },
      "qn9": {
        "answer": "Autumn",
        "options": [
          "January",
          "Autumn",
          "Winter",
          "Thursday"
        ],
        "question": "Autunno"
      }
    },
    "level3": {
      "qn1": {
        "answer": "I believe in you",
        "options": [
          "Eleven minus three is eight",
          "Good morning",
          "I believe in you",
          "I'm married"
        ],
        "question": "Credo in te"
      },
      "qn10": {
        "answer": "Can you help me?",
        "options": [
          "Can you help me?",
          "Excuse me, what did you say?",
          "What does this say?",
          "Can you do me a favor?"
        ],
        "question": "Puoi aiutarmi?"
      },
      "qn2": {
        "answer": "Waitress",
        "options": [
          "Are you sure?",
          "Which one?",
          "Waitress!",
          "One like that"
        ],
        "question": "Cameriera!"
      },
      "qn3": {
        "answer": "Where are you going?",
        "options": [
          "Are you hungry?",
          "Where is the bank?",
          "Where are you going?",
          "Where is he from?"
        ],
        "question": "Dove stai andando?"
      },
      "qn4": {
        "answer": "Which one is the best?",
        "options": [
          "Which one is the best?",
          "Anything else?",
          "How much is this?",
          "Do you believe that?"
        ],
        "question": "Qual é il migliore?"
      },
      "qn5": {
        "answer": "Are you comfortable?",
        "options": [
          "Are you hungry?",
          "Are you comfortable?",
          "Have you arrived?",
          "Where is the hospital?"
        ],
        "question": "Sei a tuo agio?"
      },
      "qn6": {
        "answer": "You're very nice",
        "options": [
          "You're very nice",
          "I made a mistake",
          "The United States has fifty states",
          "Someone does that for me"
        ],
        "question": "Sei molto carino."
      },
      "qn7": {
        "answer": "What's the temperature?",
        "options": [
          "What is the weather like in Beijing?",
          "What's the temperature?",
          "Can it be cheaper?",
          "Do you like basketball?"
        ],
        "question": "Qual é la temperatura?"
      },
      "qn8": {
        "answer": "Happy Birthday",
        "options": [
          "Happy Birthday",
          "This is very important",
          "That smells bad",
          "Everything is ready"
        ],
        "question": "Buon compleanno"
      },
      "qn9": {
        "answer": "I'm bored",
        "options": [
          "Thank you sir",
          "I'm bored",
          "You're very nice",
          "Thanks for everything"
        ],
        "question": "Sono annoiato"
      }
    }
  },
  "spanish": {
    "level1": {
      "qn1": {
        "answer": "Neighborhood",
        "options": [
          "Management",
          "Labor",
          "Neighborhood",
          "Daughter"
        ],
        "question": "Barrio"
      },
      "qn10": {
        "answer": "Flat",
        "options": [
          "Permanent",
          "Flat",
          "Low",
          "Brief"
        ],
        "question": "Plana"
      },
      "qn2": {
        "answer": "Behavior",
        "options": [
          "Medicine",
          "Point",
          "Behavior",
          "Training"
        ],
        "question": "Comportamiento"
      },
      "qn3": {
        "answer": "Sugar",
        "options": [
          "Practice",
          "Investment",
          "Sugar",
          "Baby"
        ],
        "question": "Azúcar"
      },
      "qn4": {
        "answer": "Committee",
        "options": [
          "Support",
          "Income",
          "Committee",
          "Museum"
        ],
        "question": "Comité"
      },
      "qn5": {
        "answer": "Disease",
        "options": [
          "Organization",
          "Change",
          "Disease",
          "Freedom"
        ],
        "question": "Enfermedad"
      },
      "qn6": {
        "answer": "Father",
        "options": [
          "Report",
          "Leader",
          "Father",
          "Concern"
        ],
        "question": "Padre"
      },
      "qn7": {
        "answer": "Manager",
        "options": [
          "Rock",
          "Murder",
          "Manager",
          "Truth"
        ],
        "question": "Gerente"
      },
      "qn8": {
        "answer": "Aware",
        "options": [
          "Aware",
          "Monthly",
          "Numerous",
          "Practical"
        ],
        "question": "Enterado"
      },
      "qn9": {
        "answer": "Appropriate",
        "options": [
          "Appropriate",
          "Modest",
          "Challenging",
          "Scared"
        ],
        "question": "Apropiada"
      }
    },
    "level2": {
      "qn1": {
        "answer": "Ten",
        "options": [
          "Million",
          "Twenty",
          "Ten",
          "Billion"
        ],
        "question": "Diez"
      },
      "qn10": {
        "answer": "February",
        "options": [
          "June",
          "Autumn",
          "February",
          "July"
        ],
        "question": "Febrero"
      },
      "qn2": {
        "answer": "Hundred",
        "options": [
          "Seventeen",
          "Hundred",
          "Three",
          "Eighteen"
        ],
        "question": "Cien"
      },
      "qn3": {
        "answer": "Fifty",
        "options": [
          "Zero",
          "Eight",
          "Fifty",
          "Million"
        ],
        "question": "Cincuenta"
      },
      "qn4": {
        "answer": "Hang",
        "options": [
          "Adjust",
          "Hang",
          "State",
          "Refuse"
        ],
        "question": "Colgar"
      },
      "qn5": {
        "answer": "Hide",
        "options": [
          "Accept",
          "Hide",
          "Limit",
          "Deliver"
        ],
        "question": "Esconder"
      },
      "qn6": {
        "answer": "Trust",
        "options": [
          "Spend",
          "Save",
          "Trust",
          "Shake"
        ],
        "question": "Confiar"
      },
      "qn7": {
        "answer": "Rub",
        "options": [
          "Rub",
          "Hold",
          "Breathe",
          "Help"
        ],
        "question": "Frotar"
      },
      "qn8": {
        "answer": "Beat",
        "options": [
          "Continue",
          "Beat",
          "Respond",
          "Insert"
        ],
        "question": "Ganar"
      },
      "qn9": {
        "answer": "Wednesday",
        "options": [
          "Monday",
          "Wednesday",
          "August",
          "Friday"
        ],
        "question": "Miercoles"
      }
    },
    "level3": {
      "qn1": {
        "answer": "A little",
        "options": [
          "Try it",
          "A little",
          "Tell me",
          "Never mind"
        ],
        "question": "Un poco"
      },
      "qn10": {
        "answer": "That's fine",
        "options": [
          "She is smart",
          "I don't want that",
          "That's fine",
          "Sounds good"
        ],
        "question": "Esté bien"
      },
      "qn2": {
        "answer": "Don't do that",
        "options": [
          "Follow me",
          "Don't do that",
          "Never mind",
          "I believe in you"
        ],
        "question": "No hagas eso"
      },
      "qn3": {
        "answer": "Here it is",
        "options": [
          "Here it is",
          "I'm sick",
          "Be quiet",
          "I'm married"
        ],
        "question": "Aqui estå"
      },
      "qn4": {
        "answer": "Every week",
        "options": [
          "Over there",
          "I'm sick",
          "Every week",
          "Okay"
        ],
        "question": "Todas las semanas"
      },
      "qn5": {
        "answer": "We're late",
        "options": [
          "We're late",
          "Please count this for me",
          "You're very nice",
          "I still have a lot to do"
        ],
        "question": "Vamos tarde"
      },
      "qn6": {
        "answer": "You're beautiful",
        "options": [
          "I've already seen it",
          "I have a lot of things to do",
          "You're beautiful",
          "Be careful"
        ],
        "question": "Eres hermosa"
      },
      "qn7": {
        "answer": "I don't have a boyfriend",
        "options": [
          "I don't have a boyfriend",
          "That's too many",
          "I've been there",
          "I understand"
        ],
        "question": "No tengo novio"
      },
      "qn8": {
        "answer": "No, thank you",
        "options": [
          "Next time",
          "I believe you",
          "No, thank you",
          "I know"
        ],
        "question": "No, gracias"
      },
      "qn9": {
        "answer": "Come here",
        "options": [
          "I'm single",
          "Come here",
          "No",
          "I dont know"
        ],
        "question": "Ven aqui"
      }
    }
  }
}